<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IN2000_team42</string>
    <string name="action_remove_project">Remove Project</string>
    <string name="action_save_project">Save Project</string>
    <string name="language_norwegian">Norwegian</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>
    <string name="company_name_otovo">Otovo</string>
    <string name="label_installation_guide">Installation\nGuide</string>
    <string name="label_faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="setting_dark_theme">Dark Theme</string>
    <string name="screen_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="start_screen_intro">To get started, search for an address in the field above and tap on the building that will be installed with solar panels.</string>
    <string name="start_screen_welcome">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="label_saved_project_address">Address: %1$s</string>
    <string name="label_saved_projects">Saved Projects</string>
    <string name="text_no_saved_projects">When you save a project, it will appear here.</string>
    <string name="label_recommended_products">Recommended Products</string>
    <string name="text_have_a_question">Any questions?</string>
    <string name="nav_saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="faq_1_question">Why is this app being developed?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_answer">The app helps users calculate the expected electricity production from solar panels based on local climate data, roof conditions, and solar panel efficiency.</string>
    <string name="faq_2_question">How can solar cells work effectively in Norway?</string>
    <string name="faq_2_answer">Although one might think solar cells work best in warm climates, they are most effective at around -5°C and perform poorly at temperatures above 25°C. In Southern Norway, solar cells can actually produce more energy than in Africa, as long as there is no snow cover.</string>
    <string name="faq_3_question">Can I get support for solar panel installation?</string>
    <string name="faq_3_answer">Enova offers support of up to 32,500 Norwegian kroner for electricity production that can be fed back to the power grid. It is also possible to get support for holiday homes.</string>
    <string name="faq_4_question">Can I trust the calculations in the app?</string>
    <string name="faq_4_answer">The app is based on available data and documented calculation models, but values may deviate from actual conditions. It is always recommended to compare the results with multiple sources.</string>
    <string name="faq_5_question">What is the difference between the various panels?</string>
    <string name="faq_5_answer">Solar panels and solar roof tiles are the two most common types of solar cells in Norway. Solar panels are mounted on existing roofs and cost between 2,500 and 3,000 kroner per m². They provide slightly more effect per panel than solar roof tiles but often cover a smaller part of the roof surface. Solar roof tiles replace regular roof tiles and cost between 4,000 and 5,000 kroner per m². They are especially beneficial during roof renovation, as they function both as a roof and a solar cell, which can provide a total cost savings. They are also known for a more aesthetic and discreet expression.</string>
    <string name="faq_dialog_title">FAQ</string>
    <string name="faq_dialog_close">Close</string>
    <string name="installation_guide_title">Solar Panel Guide</string>

    <string name="installation_subtitle_self_installation">Can you install solar panels yourself?</string>
    <string name="installation_self_installation_description">You cannot install solar panels yourself, except in certain cases. We strongly recommend using professionals for larger solar panel systems for homes and cabins connected to the power grid.\n\nThis ensures that the system is correctly installed, without fire and health risks. You can also be confident that the solar cells will function optimally.</string>

    <string name="installation_subtitle_when_self_install">When can you install by yourself?</string>
    <string name="installation_self_install_conditions">1. It is a standalone solar panel system\n2. You are not connected to the power grid\n3. The solar panel system is under 50V and 200VA\n4. You do not want to apply for Enova support</string>

    <string name="installation_subtitle_mounting_steps">Installation - Step by Step</string>
    <string name="installation_step_1_title">1. Assess the possibility of a solar cell system</string>
    <string name="installation_step_1_description">Before installing solar panels, check if it is permitted in your municipality. Some places require an application or have restrictions. Also, ensure that the roof is in good condition and has good sun exposure. A solar cell dealer can help you with the assessment.</string>

    <string name="installation_step_2_title">2. Choose a dealer and installer</string>
    <string name="installation_step_2_description">Choose a dealer and installer who work together for a smooth process. The dealer will help you find the right solar cell system, and most work with certified installers. This reduces the risk of misunderstandings and conflicts.</string>

    <string name="installation_step_3_title">3. Panel installation</string>
    <string name="installation_step_3_description">The installer first mounts suitable fixtures on the roof, adapted to the material and slope. Then, the solar panels are securely fastened to withstand both strong winds and heavy snow.</string>

    <string name="installation_step_4_title">4. Securing and connection</string>
    <string name="installation_step_4_description">The inverter makes the solar energy from your panels usable in your home\'s electrical outlets. The installer places the inverter in a suitable location and draws cables from the panels, which are then connected to the inverter.</string>
    <string name="Home_screen_button_calculate_production">Calculate yearly production</string>
</resources>